Siri Linnea Moström

Profile

UX-student. Creative to the backbone. Curious. Crochet-lover, Dedicated team-player. Quick learner.

Contact

Send me an email at mostromsiri(at)gmail.com

Or if you prefer some good old Linkedin-lurking, click here!

Skills

UX design

UI design

User Research

Audits

Trello

Figma

Photoshop

Balsamiq

Design Thinking

Scrum

Basic HTML

Windows Office

Swedish

English

Education

IT-högskolan

UX/UI-design. Main topics: Agile Methodology, Business benefits with design, User-centered design & Interface design & prototype

Aug 2021- present Gothenburg

Lund University

Media and communication studies. Main topics: The Societal Conditions of Communication, Media Supply, Media Use in Everyday Life, Communication and Interaction.

Sep 2019 - Jan 2020 Lund

Experience

Warehouse worker | KappAhl

Prepares and packaging orders at the e-commerce. Training for new employees. Handles returns received.

Oct 2020 - present Mölndal

UX-design intern | Bridget

Aug 2022 - Sept 2022 Gothenburg Conducted user tests. Made audits of several websites and e-commerces. Provided user journey feedback for new sketches. Participated in briefs and

communicated with customers on my own.

Projects

DataTjej

DataTjej is a Swedish non-profit organization that works to inspire more women and non-binary to start their careers in IT and data. And to unite those who are already working or studying within IT/Tech. We have around 1346 members now and we wish to continue growing.

In my role, I am responsible for DataTjejs contacts with different companies in Gothenburg, aiming to organize events, where we bring together girls and technology.

